# SEAN BLOMMAERT

SENIOR DRUPAL DEVELOPER http://www.seanblommaert.nl

#### **SUMMARY**

Sean Patrick Blommaert August 3, 1985

T: +316 2462 5019 E: info@seanblommaert.nl An experienced software developer with a passion for Drupal and Open Source. Acquia Certified backend developer, loves working on challenging projects with talented people. Excels as an intermediary between technology and business. Focused on writing high-performance, maintainable, clean and secure code. Motivated problem solver, team lead and mentor. Active Drupal (core) contributor, maintainer of the Media module in Drupal 8 core.

#### **SKILLS**

Expertise Drupal development / Team lead / Software architecture / System

integration / Security / Training

Soft skills Analytical / Communicative / Flexible / Result-oriented / Team player

CMS Drupal

Programming PHP/JavaScript/jQuery/SQL/HTML5/CSS/SASS

System integration REST / SOAP / SAML2 / Oauth

Drupal modules Media / Paragraphs / Search API / Facets / Migrate / Group / Webform

Software Git / Drush / PHPStorm / Docker / JIRA / Apache Solr / Memcache / Redis /

Apache / NGINX / Varnish

Databases MySQL/PostgreSQL/Oracle

Operating Systems Mac OS / Ubuntu / Debian / Windows

Languages Dutch (native) / English

## **EXPERIENCE**

2017 - present Freelance Drupal Developer

As a freelance developer I worked on projects in different roles. Mainly as senior backend developer, but also as an architect and frontend developer for companies such as Acquia, Skunk Works, ezCompany and LimoenGroen. In many cases as part of an on-site Scrum team, but also as part of

international remote teams.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Drupal core
- UFC (ufc.com)
- Erasmus University (eur.nl)
- 24 Kitchen (24kitchen.nl)

201	12	- 2	$\cap$ 1	7
/ ( )	١.٦	- /		/

## Senior Software Engineer, Finalist

Lead developer and Drupal architect for a wide range of projects. Involved in the recruitment/hiring process and training/coaching junior/medior developers.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Utrecht University (uu.nl)
- Maastricht University (maastrichtuniversity.nl)
- Amsterdam Museum (amsterdammuseum.nl)
- Nedap Security (nedapsecurity.com)

2008 - 2013

## Drupal Developer, Total Active Media

Responsible for technical design, implementation and maintenance of a wide range of Drupal applications.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Sound and Vision Institute (beeldengeluid.nl)
- ConQuaestor (financeincorporated.nl and conquaestor.nl)
- National Maritime Museum (hetscheepvaartmuseum.nl)
- ROC Midden Nederland (rocmn.nl)

2006 - 2008

## Jr. SAP consultant, Nuon ICT

Responsible for architecture, configuration and maintenance of multiple SAP Enterprise environments.

2004 - 2006

## Coldfusion developer, Zappwerk (internship)

Involved in the design and implementation of several high profile websites.

Some examples of developed applications are:

- Intertoys (intertoys.nl)
- Dutchs Museum Association (museum.nl)
- Utrecht University (uu.nl)
- Cultuurnet Vlaanderen, Flemish government (cultuurnet.be)

#### **EDUCATION**

0047

2017	Acquia Certified Developer - Back end Specialist (D8)
2016	Acquia Certified Developer - Back end Specialist (D7)
2014	Acquia Certified Developer (D7)
2007	Technical Consultant SAP Netweaver '04 - SAP Web AS for Oracle, SAP Netherlands
2002 - 2006	Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology, The Hague University